<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Security on AppleShare IT</title><link>https://appleshare.it/tags/security/</link><description>Recent content in Security on AppleShare IT</description><image><url>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://appleshare.it/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automating CIS Benchmark Reporting and Remediation | MacSysAdmin 2021</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/macsysadminscis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/macsysadminscis/</guid><description>I am so honoured to present at the online Mac Sys Admin this year.
This presentation is about: Automating CIS Benchmark with reporting and remediation.
Learn about a better, faster, and easier way to report and remediate CIS Benchmarks. We will introduce a new reporting script, with optional remediation. This script is designed for Big Sur and Monterey and has flexible deployment options for Jamf Pro.
Presentation Video
Slides</description></item><item><title>CIS-Script</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-script/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-script/</guid><description>This CIS Script is build to report and remediate based on the your organisation score.
While working with CIS Benchmarks (Remediation Scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt this could be done better, faster and easier. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance and configuration profiles.
I created custom rules set for CIS Benchmark to integrate with the macOS Security Compliance Project and published CIS-macOS-Security.</description></item><item><title>CIS Custom Rules Set mSCP</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-custom-rules-set-mscp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-custom-rules-set-mscp/</guid><description>While working with CIS Benchmarks PDF (guidelines for scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt there must be a better and faster way. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance, needed scripts, configuration profiles, and remediation script.
While working with CIS Benchmarks PDF (guidelines for scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt there must be a better and faster way. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance, needed scripts, configuration profiles, and remediation script.</description></item><item><title>CIS-Reporting</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-reporting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-reporting/</guid><description>github.com/mvdbent/CIS-Reporting
While i was working with Jamf&amp;rsquo;s CIS Benchmark, Script and Configuration Profile Remediation tool, I had the feeling there was missing a overview with compleet reporting. You can find some info by the device record in Jamf, however this was only for the Non-compliant items.
To expand the Jamf Proffessional Services CIS for macOS Catalina - Script and Configuration Profile Remediation, I created the 4_Security_Report.sh.
Usage/Requirements This script is tested on macOS Big Sur 11.</description></item><item><title>Securely Store Passwords</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/securely-store-passwords/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/securely-store-passwords/</guid><description>Securely store Passwords into the macOS Keychain Why put cleartext passwords in scripts, when we can use the macOS Keychain to securely store this information for us.
How to have a easy way to include this into your scripts, so we can have a placeholder for the password rather then leaking this password within the script.
How to We are going to add an PASSWORD into the macOS Keychain with the security command.</description></item></channel></rss>