<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on AppleShare IT</title>
    
    
    
    <link>/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on AppleShare IT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Powered by Hugo • Made with &amp;#10084; © 2021 • MvdBent</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CIS-Script</title>
      <link>/post/cis-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cis-script/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          This CIS Script is build to report and remediate based on the your organisation score.
While working with CIS Benchmarks (Remediation Scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt this could be done better, faster and easier. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance and configuration profiles.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIS Custom Rules Set mSCP</title>
      <link>/post/cis-custom-rules-set-mscp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cis-custom-rules-set-mscp/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          While working with CIS Benchmarks PDF (guidelines for scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt there must be a better and faster way. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance, needed scripts, configuration profiles, and remediation script.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIS-Reporting</title>
      <link>/post/cis-reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cis-reporting/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          While i was working with Jamf&#39;s CIS Benchmark, Script and Configuration Profile Remediation tool ), I had the feeling there was missing a overview with compleet reporting. You can find some info by the device record in Jamf, however this was only for the Non-compliant items.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securely Store Passwords</title>
      <link>/post/securely-store-passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/securely-store-passwords/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Why put cleartext passwords in scripts, when we can use the macOS Keychain to securely store this information for us.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>