<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Jamf Pro on AppleShare IT</title><link>https://appleshare.it/tags/jamf-pro/</link><description>Recent content in Jamf Pro on AppleShare IT</description><image><url>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://appleshare.it/tags/jamf-pro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automating CIS Benchmark Reporting and Remediation</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/automating-cis-benchmark/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/automating-cis-benchmark/</guid><description>Learn about a better, faster and easier way to report and remediate CIS Benchmarks. We will introduce a new reporting script, with optional remediation. This script is designed for Big Sur and Monterey and has flexible deployment options for Jamf Pro.
Resources Jamf Blog
CIS-Script Blog
CIS-Script GitHub
Center for Internet Security, Inc. (CIS®)
macOS Security Compliance Project
Jamf Compliance Editor</description></item><item><title>Jamf Nation Live 2022</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/jnl22/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/jnl22/</guid><description>Jamf Nation Live is back after a two-year hiatus! We kicked off the 2022 tour in London-style at the Great Gallery in Tobacco Dock. We had a great time and presented at all locations. Check out the videos below for an impression of JNL22, and we hope to see you next year!
Jamf Nation Live - London Jamf Nation Live - Amsterdam Jamf Nation Live - Paris Jamf Nation Live - München Resources Jamf Blog</description></item><item><title>How to use dockutil in a script</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/use-dockutil-in-a-script/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/use-dockutil-in-a-script/</guid><description>Now that dockutil has been rewritten in Swift for macOS 12.3 compatibility, I needed to dust off my scripts. dockutil is supporting macOS 11 Big Sur or higher.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to look at the USAGE section in the readme or use the --help option to read more about the usage and options.
Luckily, not much is needed to be dusted off. However, I wanted to add some adjustments and share my workflows which you can use within Jamf.</description></item><item><title>CIS-Script</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-script/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-script/</guid><description>This CIS Script is build to report and remediate based on the your organisation score.
While working with CIS Benchmarks (Remediation Scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt this could be done better, faster and easier. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance and configuration profiles.
I created custom rules set for CIS Benchmark to integrate with the macOS Security Compliance Project and published CIS-macOS-Security.</description></item><item><title>onAirScanner</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/onairscanner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/onairscanner/</guid><description>While working from home, we all have a lot of meetings, and sometimes a family member or a roommate has no idea that you are in a meeting and they walk into the room without even a knock. Setting up a light to show when you are &amp;ldquo;ON AIR&amp;rdquo; or in a meeting is a great solution. There are several solutions out on the internet that can do this. Still, a lot of these solutions connect to your calendar via IFTTT or Zapier and then you need to create an action with homekit or homebridge to turn on a light with the colour red when in a meeting and green when it is safe to enter.</description></item></channel></rss>