<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AppleShare IT</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AppleShare IT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>mvdbent</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About the Author</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there,
My name is Mischa van der Bent and this is my personal blog and mainly write about sharing my experience with Apple IT related matters and share what I think is interesting to share.
 Disclaimer: all posts, opinions, suggestions, remarks, information or statements of any kind, are my own. My current employer Jamf, or any other 3rd party mentioned in, or linked to, any part of this blog, can never be held responsible for the information on this website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIS-Script</title>
      <link>/posts/2021/10/cis-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021/10/cis-script/</guid>
      <description>This blog is about the CIS-Script
#!/bin/zsh  export PATH=/usr/bin:/bin:/usr/sbin:/sbin #################################################################################################### #################################################################################################### # DESCRIPTION # This will upload CIS Benchmark Scoring CSV to the computer record #################################################################################################### #################################################################################################### if [ &amp;#34;$4&amp;#34; != &amp;#34;&amp;#34; ] &amp;amp;&amp;amp; [ &amp;#34;$basic_auth&amp;#34; == &amp;#34;&amp;#34; ]; then basic_auth=$4 else echo &amp;#34;basic_auth is unset, please insert base64-encoded credentials within Parameter 4 in Jamf Pro&amp;#34; exit 1 fi should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Change your submodule to point to map gh-pages to public instead of _site (recommended).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EraseInstall application retired</title>
      <link>/posts/2021/03/eraseinstall-application-retired/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021/03/eraseinstall-application-retired/</guid>
      <description>It makes me very sad that the EraseInstall application has been retired.
We built this tool three years ago, mostly because we wanted to learn how to build an app like this on macOS. We think it worked out well. We learned a lot, and are glad the application was useful to some.
Since then, all the people involved in the EraseInstall Project have moved on to other jobs or other responsibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>onAirScanner</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/10/onairscanner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/10/onairscanner/</guid>
      <description>SOURCE onAirScanner - GitHub While working from home, we all have a lot of meetings, and sometimes a family member or a roommate has no idea that you are in a meeting and they walk into the room without even a knock. Setting up a light to show when you are &amp;ldquo;ON AIR&amp;rdquo; or in a meeting is a great solution. There are several solutions out on the internet that can do this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off-boarding in a Modern Deployment | JNUC 2019</title>
      <link>/posts/2019/11/off-boarding-in-a-modern-deployment-jnuc-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019/11/off-boarding-in-a-modern-deployment-jnuc-2019/</guid>
      <description>Imaging is dead. Secure Boot and the T2 system controller have changed the toolset available to Mac administrators. The new post-imaging world of Mojave requires new workflows. We learn about the role that &amp;lsquo;off-boarding&amp;rsquo; or the erase/install step has in the modern macOS deployment cycle. In this session, we will explore the startosinstall command in detail and learn about its uses and limitations. Finally, we will introduce a few workflows and tools (Erase&amp;amp;Install.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automation Panel | JNUC 2018</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/10/automation-panel-jnuc-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/10/automation-panel-jnuc-2018/</guid>
      <description>In this JNUC session, we talk through some of the details of automating various components of your Apple environment.
How to automate your &amp;ldquo;favorite&amp;rdquo; workflows. Let’s face it — one of the main reasons many people come to the Jamf Nation User Conference (JNUC) is to automate the crap out of their environment and have it run like a well-oiled machine. In this panel, we talk through some of the details of automating various components of your Apple environment, including Jamf.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
