<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AppleShare IT</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AppleShare IT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>mvdbent</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/09/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/09/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>/posts/2019/03/migrate-to-hugo-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019/03/migrate-to-hugo-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there,
My name is Mischa van der Bent and I&amp;rsquo;m the author of this Blog. This is my personal blog and mainly write about sharing my experience with Apple IT related matters and share what I think is interesting to share.
 Disclaimer: all posts, opinions, suggestions, remarks, information or statements of any kind, are my own. My current employee Jamf, or any other 3rd party mentioned in, or linked to, any part of this blog, can never be held responsible for the information on this website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIS-Script</title>
      <link>/posts/2021/10/cis-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021/10/cis-script/</guid>
      <description>This blog is about the CIS-Script
#!/bin/zsh  export PATH=/usr/bin:/bin:/usr/sbin:/sbin #################################################################################################### #################################################################################################### # DESCRIPTION # This will upload CIS Benchmark Scoring CSV to the computer record #################################################################################################### #################################################################################################### if [ &amp;#34;$4&amp;#34; != &amp;#34;&amp;#34; ] &amp;amp;&amp;amp; [ &amp;#34;$basic_auth&amp;#34; == &amp;#34;&amp;#34; ]; then basic_auth=$4 else echo &amp;#34;basic_auth is unset, please insert base64-encoded credentials within Parameter 4 in Jamf Pro&amp;#34; exit 1 fi should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Change your submodule to point to map gh-pages to public instead of _site (recommended).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/12/getting-started-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/12/getting-started-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/04/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/04/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
