<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Bash on AppleShare IT</title><link>https://appleshare.it/tags/bash/</link><description>Recent content in Bash on AppleShare IT</description><image><url>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://appleshare.it/tags/bash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy packages during prestage with a Manifest file</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/use-manifest-file/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/use-manifest-file/</guid><description>When you upload a package to Jamf Pro, and you are using a JCDS as a distribution point, a manifest file gets automatically created. If your environment uses an HTTPS server that is NOT a Jamf Pro HTTPS-capable distribution point to host your packages, the requirements are to create a custom manifest file and upload it along with the Signed Distribution Package into Jamf Pro.
Before we start with covering the manifest file, I want to highlight that we need a Signed Distribution Package.</description></item><item><title>How to use dockutil in a script</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/use-dockutil-in-a-script/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/use-dockutil-in-a-script/</guid><description>Now that dockutil has been rewritten in Swift for macOS 12.3 compatibility, I needed to dust off my scripts. dockutil is supporting macOS 11 Big Sur or higher.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to look at the USAGE section in the readme or use the --help option to read more about the usage and options.
Luckily, not much is needed to be dusted off. However, I wanted to add some adjustments and share my workflows which you can use within Jamf.</description></item><item><title>Automating CIS Benchmark Reporting and Remediation | MacSysAdmin 2021</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/macsysadminscis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/macsysadminscis/</guid><description>I am so honoured to present at the online Mac Sys Admin this year.
This presentation is about: Automating CIS Benchmark with reporting and remediation.
Learn about a better, faster, and easier way to report and remediate CIS Benchmarks. We will introduce a new reporting script, with optional remediation. This script is designed for Big Sur and Monterey and has flexible deployment options for Jamf Pro.
Presentation Video
Slides</description></item><item><title>Securely Store Passwords</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/securely-store-passwords/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/securely-store-passwords/</guid><description>Securely store Passwords into the macOS Keychain Why put cleartext passwords in scripts, when we can use the macOS Keychain to securely store this information for us.
How to have a easy way to include this into your scripts, so we can have a placeholder for the password rather then leaking this password within the script.
How to We are going to add an PASSWORD into the macOS Keychain with the security command.</description></item></channel></rss>