<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Meetup on AppleShare IT</title><link>https://appleshare.it/tags/meetup/</link><description>Recent content in Meetup on AppleShare IT</description><image><url>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://appleshare.it/tags/meetup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>It's Jamf Nation Live 2023 time!</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/dutch-mac-admins-xebia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/dutch-mac-admins-xebia/</guid><description>This year Jamf is coming to London (9th June), RheinMain (13th June), Paris (15th June) and last location will be Amsterdam (20th June).
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t registered yet, make sure you register below!
London @ Taets Art and Event Park RheinMain @ RheinMain CongressCenter, Wiesbaden Paris @ 3 Mazarium Amsterdam @ Taets Art and Event Park Can't wait to see you in person at one of the locations! Therefore, I want to provide some useful information that can help you if you are coming to one of the events!</description></item><item><title>Dutch Mac Admins Meetup at Xebia</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/jamf-nation-life-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/jamf-nation-life-2023/</guid><description>Our Second in-person Hybrid Dutch Mac Admins Meetup was hosted by Xebia, they have enough space and the facilities to host this meeting both on location and remote (hybrid), this allows everyone to join where they feel comfortable.
Marlon Soekhar, Manager IT by Xebia, kickof the evening and told us what his team does and told us more about Xebia, who they are and what they do.
Introduces the new App Catalog by Root3 The first presentation was held by Jordy Witteman, Apple Principal Consultant by Root3.</description></item><item><title>Dutch Mac Admins Meetup at Adyen</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/dutch-mac-admins-adyen/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/dutch-mac-admins-adyen/</guid><description>After a long periode, we finally organized a in-person Hybrid Dutch Mac Admins Meetup. It was great to see everyone
Mac Device Managament @ Adyen We started with Adyen, the team told us about who they are and how they Onboard and migrate their Mac estate within their environment and share their challenges and how they resolve them.
The Mac Admins Foundation The second presentation is about the Mac Admins Foundation, we had the founders presenting the foundation!</description></item></channel></rss>