<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>macOS on AppleShare IT</title>
    
    
    
    <link>/tags/macos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in macOS on AppleShare IT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Powered by Hugo • Made with &amp;#10084; © 2021 • MvdBent</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/macos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating CIS Benchmark Reporting and Remediation | MacSysAdmin 2021</title>
      <link>/post/macsysadminscis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/macsysadminscis/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          I am so honoured to present at the online MacSysAdmin this year. My online presentation is about Automating CIS Benchmark with reporting and remediation. Learn about a better, faster, and easier way to report and remediate CIS Benchmarks
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIS-Script</title>
      <link>/post/cis-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cis-script/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          This CIS Script is build to report and remediate based on the your organisation score.
While working with CIS Benchmarks (Remediation Scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt this could be done better, faster and easier. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance and configuration profiles.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIS Custom Rules Set mSCP</title>
      <link>/post/cis-custom-rules-set-mscp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cis-custom-rules-set-mscp/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          While working with CIS Benchmarks PDF (guidelines for scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt there must be a better and faster way. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance, needed scripts, configuration profiles, and remediation script.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EraseInstall application retired</title>
      <link>/post/eraseinstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/eraseinstall/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          It makes me very sad that the [**EraseInstall application**](https://bitbucket.org/prowarehouse-nl/erase-install/) has been retired.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIS-Reporting</title>
      <link>/post/cis-reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cis-reporting/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          While i was working with Jamf&#39;s CIS Benchmark, Script and Configuration Profile Remediation tool ), I had the feeling there was missing a overview with compleet reporting. You can find some info by the device record in Jamf, however this was only for the Non-compliant items.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>onAirScanner</title>
      <link>/post/onairscanner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/onairscanner/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          While working from home, we all have a lot of meetings, and sometimes a family member or a roommate has no idea that you are in a meeting and they walk into the room without even a knock. Setting up a light to show when you are &#34;ON AIR&#34; or in a meeting is a great solution.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The story of trust destroyed | JNUC 2020</title>
      <link>/post/thestoryoftrustdestroyed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/thestoryoftrustdestroyed/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          The truth about MDM Migration: Journey through time as Jamf consulting engineers Mischa van der Bent and Rob Potvin talk about the current design of the Apple MDM protocol and what the migration process looks like for moving existing devices from one MDM to another. This can be fairly difficult, but success is possible with a bit of time, effort and planning. It is not really migrating, but destroying trust.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securely Store Passwords</title>
      <link>/post/securely-store-passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/securely-store-passwords/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Why put cleartext passwords in scripts, when we can use the macOS Keychain to securely store this information for us.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off-boarding in a Modern Deployment | JNUC 2019</title>
      <link>/post/off-boarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/off-boarding/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Imaging is dead. Secure Boot and the T2 system controller have changed the toolset available to Mac administrators. The new post-imaging world of Mojave requires new workflows.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>