<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on AppleShare IT</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on AppleShare IT</description><image><url>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://appleshare.it/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>It's Jamf Nation Live 2023 time!</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/jamf-nation-life-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/jamf-nation-life-2023/</guid><description>This year Jamf Nation Live is coming to London (9th June), RheinMain (13th June), Paris (15th June) and last location will be Amsterdam (20th June).
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t registered yet, make sure you register below!
London @ Taets Art and Event Park RheinMain @ RheinMain CongressCenter, Wiesbaden Paris @ 3 Mazarium Amsterdam @ Taets Art and Event Park Can't wait to see you in person at one of the locations!</description></item><item><title>Dutch Mac Admins Meetup at Fremantle</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/dutch-mac-admins-fremantle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/dutch-mac-admins-fremantle/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to meet again, and this time we&amp;rsquo;re meeting in person only. Fremantle Netherlands has kindly offered to host this meeting, and they have ample space and facilities to accommodate us.
We are excited to announce that on Monday, the 19th of June, we will be holding a MacAdmins meeting from 17:30 to 21:00.
To secure your spot, please register yourself as soon as possible. Please note that there are limited places available, so don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on this opportunity!</description></item><item><title>Dutch Mac Admins Meetup at Xebia</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/dutch-mac-admins-xebia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/dutch-mac-admins-xebia/</guid><description>Our Second in-person Hybrid Dutch Mac Admins Meetup was hosted by Xebia, they have enough space and the facilities to host this meeting both on location and remote (hybrid), this allows everyone to join where they feel comfortable.
Marlon Soekhar, Manager IT by Xebia, kickof the evening and told us what his team does and told us more about Xebia, who they are and what they do.
Introduces the new App Catalog by Root3 The first presentation was held by Jordy Witteman, Apple Principal Consultant by Root3.</description></item><item><title>Automating CIS Benchmark Reporting and Remediation</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/automating-cis-benchmark/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/automating-cis-benchmark/</guid><description>Learn about a better, faster and easier way to report and remediate CIS Benchmarks. We will introduce a new reporting script, with optional remediation. This script is designed for Big Sur and Monterey and has flexible deployment options for Jamf Pro.
Resources Jamf Blog
CIS-Script Blog
CIS-Script GitHub
Center for Internet Security, Inc. (CIS®)
macOS Security Compliance Project
Jamf Compliance Editor</description></item><item><title>Dutch Mac Admins Meetup at Adyen</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/dutch-mac-admins-adyen/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/dutch-mac-admins-adyen/</guid><description>After a long periode, we finally organized a in-person Hybrid Dutch Mac Admins Meetup. It was great to see everyone
Mac Device Managament @ Adyen We started with Adyen, the team told us about who they are and how they Onboard and migrate their Mac estate within their environment and share their challenges and how they resolve them.
The Mac Admins Foundation The second presentation is about the Mac Admins Foundation, we had the founders presenting the foundation!</description></item><item><title>Jamf Nation Live 2022</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/jnl22/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/jnl22/</guid><description>Jamf Nation Live is back after a two-year hiatus! We kicked off the 2022 tour in London-style at the Great Gallery in Tobacco Dock. We had a great time and presented at all locations. Check out the videos below for an impression of JNL22, and we hope to see you next year!
Jamf Nation Live - London Jamf Nation Live - Amsterdam Jamf Nation Live - Paris Jamf Nation Live - München Resources Jamf Blog</description></item><item><title>How to use dockutil in a script</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/use-dockutil-in-a-script/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/use-dockutil-in-a-script/</guid><description>Now that dockutil has been rewritten in Swift for macOS 12.3 compatibility, I needed to dust off my scripts. dockutil is supporting macOS 11 Big Sur or higher.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to look at the USAGE section in the readme or use the --help option to read more about the usage and options.
Luckily, not much is needed to be dusted off. However, I wanted to add some adjustments and share my workflows which you can use within Jamf.</description></item><item><title>Automating CIS Benchmark Reporting and Remediation | MacSysAdmin 2021</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/macsysadminscis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/macsysadminscis/</guid><description>I am so honoured to present at the online Mac Sys Admin this year.
This presentation is about: Automating CIS Benchmark with reporting and remediation.
Learn about a better, faster, and easier way to report and remediate CIS Benchmarks. We will introduce a new reporting script, with optional remediation. This script is designed for Big Sur and Monterey and has flexible deployment options for Jamf Pro.
Presentation Video
Slides</description></item><item><title>CIS-Script</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-script/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-script/</guid><description>This CIS Script is build to report and remediate based on the your organisation score.
While working with CIS Benchmarks (Remediation Scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt this could be done better, faster and easier. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance and configuration profiles.
I created custom rules set for CIS Benchmark to integrate with the macOS Security Compliance Project and published CIS-macOS-Security.</description></item><item><title>CIS Custom Rules Set mSCP</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-custom-rules-set-mscp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-custom-rules-set-mscp/</guid><description>While working with CIS Benchmarks PDF (guidelines for scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt there must be a better and faster way. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance, needed scripts, configuration profiles, and remediation script.
While working with CIS Benchmarks PDF (guidelines for scripts and/or Configuration Profiles) I felt there must be a better and faster way. The guys from the macOS Security Compliance Project did an amazing job automating the guidance, needed scripts, configuration profiles, and remediation script.</description></item><item><title>EraseInstall application retired</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/eraseinstall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/eraseinstall/</guid><description>It makes me very sad that the EraseInstall application has been retired.
We built this tool three years ago, mostly because we wanted to learn how to build an app like this on macOS. We think it worked out well. We learned a lot, and are glad the application was useful to some.
Since then, all the people involved in the EraseInstall Project have moved on to other jobs or other responsibilities.</description></item><item><title>CIS-Reporting</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-reporting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/cis-reporting/</guid><description>github.com/mvdbent/CIS-Reporting
While i was working with Jamf&amp;rsquo;s CIS Benchmark, Script and Configuration Profile Remediation tool, I had the feeling there was missing a overview with compleet reporting. You can find some info by the device record in Jamf, however this was only for the Non-compliant items.
To expand the Jamf Proffessional Services CIS for macOS Catalina - Script and Configuration Profile Remediation, I created the 4_Security_Report.sh.
Usage/Requirements This script is tested on macOS Big Sur 11.</description></item><item><title>onAirScanner</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/onairscanner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/onairscanner/</guid><description>While working from home, we all have a lot of meetings, and sometimes a family member or a roommate has no idea that you are in a meeting and they walk into the room without even a knock. Setting up a light to show when you are &amp;ldquo;ON AIR&amp;rdquo; or in a meeting is a great solution. There are several solutions out on the internet that can do this. Still, a lot of these solutions connect to your calendar via IFTTT or Zapier and then you need to create an action with homekit or homebridge to turn on a light with the colour red when in a meeting and green when it is safe to enter.</description></item><item><title>The story of trust destroyed | JNUC 2020</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/thestoryoftrustdestroyed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/thestoryoftrustdestroyed/</guid><description>The truth about MDM Migration: Journey through time as Jamf consulting engineer me and Rob Potvin will talk about the current design of the Apple MDM protocol and what the migration process looks like for moving existing devices from one MDM to another.
This can be fairly difficult, but success is possible with a bit of time, effort and planning. It is not really migrating, but destroying trust.
Presentation Video Tools ReEnroller</description></item><item><title>Securely Store Passwords</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/securely-store-passwords/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/securely-store-passwords/</guid><description>Securely store Passwords into the macOS Keychain Why put cleartext passwords in scripts, when we can use the macOS Keychain to securely store this information for us.
How to have a easy way to include this into your scripts, so we can have a placeholder for the password rather then leaking this password within the script.
How to We are going to add an PASSWORD into the macOS Keychain with the security command.</description></item><item><title>Off-boarding in a Modern Deployment | JNUC 2019</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/off-boarding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/off-boarding/</guid><description>Imaging is dead. Secure Boot and the T2 system controller have changed the toolset available to Mac administrators. The new post-imaging world of Mojave requires new workflows. We learn about the role that &amp;lsquo;off-boarding&amp;rsquo; or the erase/install step has in the modern macOS deployment cycle. In this session, we will explore the startosinstall command in detail and learn about its uses and limitations. Finally, we will introduce a few workflows and tools (Erase&amp;amp;Install.</description></item><item><title>Automation Panel | JNUC 2018</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/automationpanel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/automationpanel/</guid><description>In this JNUC session, we talk through some of the details of automating various components of your Apple environment.</description></item></channel></rss>