<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>presentation on AppleShare IT</title><link>https://appleshare.it/tags/presentation/</link><description>Recent content in presentation on AppleShare IT</description><image><url>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://appleshare.it/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://appleshare.it/tags/presentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automating CIS Benchmark Reporting and Remediation | MacSysAdmin 2021</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/macsysadminscis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/macsysadminscis/</guid><description>I am so honoured to present at the online Mac Sys Admin this year.
This presentation is about: Automating CIS Benchmark with reporting and remediation.
Learn about a better, faster, and easier way to report and remediate CIS Benchmarks. We will introduce a new reporting script, with optional remediation. This script is designed for Big Sur and Monterey and has flexible deployment options for Jamf Pro.
Presentation Video</description></item><item><title>The story of trust destroyed | JNUC 2020</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/thestoryoftrustdestroyed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/thestoryoftrustdestroyed/</guid><description>The truth about MDM Migration: Journey through time as Jamf consulting engineer me and Rob Potvin will talk about the current design of the Apple MDM protocol and what the migration process looks like for moving existing devices from one MDM to another.
This can be fairly difficult, but success is possible with a bit of time, effort and planning. It is not really migrating, but destroying trust.
Presentation Video Tools ReEnroller</description></item><item><title>Off-boarding in a Modern Deployment | JNUC 2019</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/off-boarding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/off-boarding/</guid><description>Imaging is dead. Secure Boot and the T2 system controller have changed the toolset available to Mac administrators. The new post-imaging world of Mojave requires new workflows. We learn about the role that &amp;lsquo;off-boarding&amp;rsquo; or the erase/install step has in the modern macOS deployment cycle. In this session, we will explore the startosinstall command in detail and learn about its uses and limitations. Finally, we will introduce a few workflows and tools (Erase&amp;amp;Install.</description></item><item><title>Automation Panel | JNUC 2018</title><link>https://appleshare.it/posts/automationpanel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appleshare.it/posts/automationpanel/</guid><description>In this JNUC session, we talk through some of the details of automating various components of your Apple environment.</description></item></channel></rss>